

LOCATION
Palm Desert
California, United States

E-MAIL & SOCIAL MEDIA benbarker0311@gmail.com Skype:live:.cid.a073e8d921211241 Website:ksanaraki.netlify.app Github:github.com/ksanaraki

PROFILE

Dedicated and efficient fullstack engineer with 6+ years experience in application layers, presentation layers and databases and be fortified with the agile methodologies, project management and verification, service delivery, project life-cycles, data gathering and code documentation.

EDUCATION

04.2013 - 03.2016

Nagoya Institute of Technology, Japan

B.S. in Computer Science

Excellent Student Paper Award (03.2015)

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

PHP

C++

JavaScript&TypeScript

HTML5

CSS

Python & Django

Go

NodeJS



SKILLS

- ✓ .NET, GraphQL, SOAP, WebRTC, Socket.io
- ✓ MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL and Firebase
- ✓ MERN Stack, MEAN Stack, PERN Stack
- ✓ Wordpress, Laravel, Ethereum, Solana and Web3.js
- ✓ AWS, Azure, Docker, Kubernetes and Git
- ✓ Nginx, Apache, Tomcat and Serverless&Cloud service
- ✓ Restful Web Services, Enterprise Service Bus, TCP/IP, UDP, HTTP/2, TSL

CERTIFICATES

- Free Code Camp Fullstack Development Certification (06.2017 09.2017)
- Frontend Web Development Certificate (2014.09)

KSAN ARAKI

Full Stack Engineer

EXPERIENCE

08.2021 - present

Senior Full Stack Engineer

Self-employed

- 12 projects related to web marketing, MERN and MEAN, Google Analytics, data analysis and SEO
- A brand-new admin panel for purchasing agent business, which improved the customer service by 90% and efficiency of operating by over 25%
- 10+ Ethereum and Solana websites such as DApp, minting and staking ... by using web3.js

05.2016 - 07.2021

Full Stack Engineer

KASUGAI Co.Ltd, Japan. (Data Engineer Group)

- Response for development, implement and maintain internal websites and services and collaborated with tech and bus staffs in the design, development, testing, implementation and production support of enterprise apps.40% of my work was frontend development, 40% backend development and the 20% was dev-ops/sysadmin tasks, migrating test DB data between envs, doing Jenkins builds/minor build plan tweaks, configuring webpack/or UI/unit testing frameworks
- Worked on RoR backend, which provides services for Back line clients. Back line is a secure messenger
- Trained and supported 8 new hires by conducting interviews, leading lectures and testing code

04.2013 - 03.2016

Student and Full Stack Developer

Nagoya Institute of Technology, Japan

- Structure DB of our department community for as part of "Data Structure and Algorithm 101" course.
- With 7 students in a paired arrangement and took part in various internship on online IT job sites.
- Digital transformation project, a web app to help with data management, accounting, and HR duties at Nagoya City University West Medical Center.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- YourNFT Hub is marketplace site for Solana chain. You can list, buy and sell your NFTs on solana. Using PERN stack with NextJS and Solana Web3.js Please visit https://yournfthub.com
- Plasbit-Crypto Card Service for Multicrypto Currency.
 With Plasbit Card, similar to visa card, you can make transfer and payment for Bitcoin, Ethereum & USDT so on. Developed with MeteorJS + MongoDB.

Please visit https://plasbit.com

